(Sheldon:)That's a risk
I'm willing to take!
(Amy:)Well, this is so nice.
(Amy:)He's so excited
to have you here and...
(Meemaw:)Okay, now let's you and me
get something straight.
(Meemaw:)He may think that I came
to bake him cookies,
(Meemaw:)but the real reason
is to size you up.
(Sheldon:)S-S...
Si-Size me up?
(Meemaw:)Sheldon's mother may be
okay with you,
(Meemaw:)but I'm not so easy.
Well, I-I'm...
(Amy:)I'm sure you'll like me
once you get to know me.
(Meemaw:)Oh, you better hope so.
(Sheldon:)A Texas Special cattle
and calf car train set
with authentic horn and bell!
Thank you, Meemaw!
(Meemaw:)Oh, you're welcome, Moon Pie.
(Sheldon:)Amy, why don't you
(Sheldon:)look excited?
(Sheldon:)Well, you get
to watch me play with this!
Oh, I see you're reading Saga.
(Girl:)Yeah, I hear it's pretty good.
(Raj:)It is, and not a lot of comics
have a woman with wings
(Raj:)breastfeeding a baby
right on the cover.